<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gavisto</title>
    <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gavisto</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 02:00:24 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.gavisto.vn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>InLab and the Turning Card for The Sightless</title>
      <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/science-and-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 02:00:24 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/science-and-technology/</guid>
      <description>Before long, the sightless people have vastly been outweighed in the playground of technology. Due to unavailability of physical condition, they are likely to face obstacles in using newly-launched softwares and programs. However, along with technology development, these difficulties have gradually faded out. With the presence of Artificial Intelligence, Artificial Voice especially, the sightless people, from this time on, are grasping a huge opportunity to touch into the world of technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NHA RONG: A House to Build A Culture On</title>
      <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 01:58:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/culture/</guid>
      <description>Vietnam is a multi-ethnic country with 54 ethnic groups living together. Kinh people account for 85.4%. In essence, the term &amp;ldquo;ethnic minority&amp;rdquo; is a term used by the Government to refer to non-Kinh people. However, one phenomenon that can be easily observed is that this concept of &amp;ldquo;ethnic minorities&amp;rdquo; is often judged by preconceptions of quality rather than quantity.
The stories of alleviation of hunger in the uplands, the patronage of the mountains, and the general invisible also become the almost unique information that we receive through information channels every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Quintessential Approach To Pluralism: Origin And Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/social/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 01:56:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/social/</guid>
      <description>“Because I am a Christian, I have formed a friendship with a Muslim&amp;rdquo; (Patel 141). The sentence daunted me for more than any book has ever done, because of the ambiguity in its utmost clarity. What is, essentially, the difference, the impact that the statement makes from the common formula: “I&amp;rsquo;m friends with a Muslim even though I’m Christian”? It turns out to me, that Eboo Patel’s book Sacred Ground: Pluralism, Prejudice, And The Promise of America sets up a profound case study on this notions and comes up with an answer to the formulas above: a triangle of knowledge, relationships and attitude (Patel 79).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Buddhist Understanding of Vocation Through Isak Dinesen’s Babette’s Feast</title>
      <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/literature/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 01:39:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/literature/</guid>
      <description>I was 7,985 miles away from home. My time zone was 12-hour different from my hometown’s. And, I was distance-wise too far away from my Buddhist tradition. At the age of nineteen, I was thriving in the environment of a Lutheran college, while wholefully believing in Buddhism. Yet, never in the over two years had I been concerned about, or disturbed because of my religious difference. Instead, I took my studying abroad as an opportunity to test my engagement with the tradition I was born into and have been bred with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Exposed Attack - Body Shaming and Cyber Insecurity</title>
      <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/an-exposed-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 00:43:04 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/an-exposed-attack/</guid>
      <description>Recently, The CEO of Facebook, Mark Zuckerberg, had to face over forty US senators about hate speech and users’ private information. The inquiries mainly concerned with the safety of Facebook users, as well as the expansion of the application&amp;rsquo;s role in human&amp;rsquo;s life. . After nearly five hours in the Supreme Court, the CEO of Facebook admitted his personal responsibility for the failure to protect users’ privacy on social networks and gave a clear explanation about his system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ahihi</title>
      <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/ahihi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 00:34:36 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/ahihi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MyBlog</title>
      <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/myblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 00:09:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gavisto.vn/blogs/myblog/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 16:03:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gavisto.vn/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Second Post</title>
      <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/posts/my-second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 16:03:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gavisto.vn/posts/my-second-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Third Post</title>
      <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/posts/my-third-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 16:03:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gavisto.vn/posts/my-third-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Người khiếm thị và cách mạng 4.0</title>
      <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/posts/my-fourth-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 16:03:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gavisto.vn/posts/my-fourth-post/</guid>
      <description>asdbgahsidghjaksdfas dasdas asdas das da sd asd asd as dasdasdasd </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Đại học Khoa học và Công nghệ Hà Nội</title>
      <link>https://www.gavisto.vn/posts/my-fifth-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 16:03:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gavisto.vn/posts/my-fifth-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>